[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my brother George.
[GRUNTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[BANGING, POUNDING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
have come to play
in Granny
and Grandpa's garden.
[CLUNKING, CLANKING]
What's that noise?
Grandpa's making something.
Hello, Peppa and George.
That's perfect timing.
[GRUNTS]
I've just finished making it.
And may we ask
what "it" is?
Hee-hee-hee.
I'll show you.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[HISSING]
PEPPA & GEORGE: Wow.
A little toy train.
It's not a toy.
This is Gertrude.
She's a miniature locomotive.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
But doesn't it need
railway tracks to run on?
Oh, no. I've fitted
Gertrude with car wheels,
so she can go anywhere
she likes.
[GRUNTS]
Grandpa, can we
ride in Gertrude?
Hop aboard.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Full steam ahead!
Bye bye, Granny.
See you later.
NARRATOR: Peppa and George love
Grandpa's little train.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
♪ Grandpa's little train goes
Choo choo choo ♪
♪ Choo choo choo
♪ Grandpa's little train goes
Choo choo choo ♪
♪ All day long ♪
♪ And the piggies on the train
Go oink oink oink ♪
♪ Oink oink oink
Oink oink oink ♪
♪ And the piggies on the train
Go oink oink oink ♪
♪ All day long ♪
[ALL LAUGH, SNORT]
[HONKING]
NARRATOR: Here is Granddad Dog
with Danny Dog.
Hello.
Hello, Danny.
Woof. I see you're
playing toy trains.
Toy? Gertrude isn't a toy.
[GRUNTS]
How's your little lorry?
Little lorry?
My breakdown truck
is a proper, work vehicle.
Granddad? Can I ride
on the train?
Hm. It's your
choice, Danny,
if you'd rather
play trains than--
Thanks, Granddad.
[GIGGLES]
See you later.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
NARRATOR: Miss Rabbit is driving
the school bus.
And to our left, we can see
some hills with trees...
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Hello, everyone.
ALL:
Hello, Peppa.
NARRATOR:
All Peppa's friends are here.
Can we ride on the train?
Um. I'm giving the children
an educational bus tour.
Are trains educational?
They certainly are.
Uh, hands up, all those who
want to ride on the train.
ALL:
Me! Me! Me!
MISS RABBIT:
And hands up, all those who
want to stay on the bus.
Okay, you can all
go on the train.
And I'll follow
along behind.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[KIDS GIGGLING]
♪ Grandpa's little train goes
Choo choo choo ♪
♪ Choo choo choo
♪ Grandpa's little train goes
Choo choo choo ♪
♪ All day long ♪
NARRATOR:
What a lot of mud.
We don't want
to get stuck.
Maybe we should go
a different way.
It's only a patch of mud.
Come on, Gertrude.
You can make it.
Come on, bus.
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
NARRATOR:
The bus is stuck in the mud.
Oh, bother.
[TRUCK HORN HONKS]
Ruff.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
How are you today?
I'm a bit stuck.
Can you rescue me?
Certainly.
Is your truck
strong enough?
Trust me.
[REVVING]
[SPLOSHING]
Did it work?
Uh. No.
We need a vehicle
with more power.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
Can I help in any way?
Uh, it's nothing that
I can't deal with.
Thanks, anyway.
I've got an idea.
Grandpa Pig's train can
tow me out of the mud.
Uh, good thinking,
Miss Rabbit.
NARRATOR:
Grandpa's little train is going
to pull the bus out of the mud.
Full steam.
ALL:
Come on, Gertrude!
[STRAINING]
KIDS:
Hooray!
Ho ho. Well done.
It's amazing what can be
done by a toy train.
Toy? Gertrude isn't a toy.
Gertrude is the very best train
in the whole world.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are visiting
their big cousin Chloé.
[GRUNTS]
Today, as well as
seeing Chloé,
you are going to
meet your new cousin.
Ooh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family have
arrived at Chloé's house.
DADDY PIG: Hello.
UNCLE PIG: Hello, everyone.
[GRUNTS]
Hello, Peppa and George.
NARRATOR: This is Chloé,
Peppa and George's big cousin.
[SNORTS]
But where's
our new cousin?
Here's your
new baby cousin.
Ooh.
NARRATOR: The new cousin
is a tiny, baby piggy.
Goo, goo, goo.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, how beautiful.
Is it a girl baby?
No, it's a boy.
Oh.
I wish it was a girl.
Me too.
[GRUNTS, GIGGLES]
NARRATOR: George is pleased
the baby is a boy.
Dine-Saw. Grrrr.
[CRYING]
[GRUNTS]
I think the baby's too little
to play with dinosaurs.
George, the baby doesn't
want to play with you.
It wants to play
with me.
[CRYING]
Peppa, the baby is much too
little to play ball games.
But if it can't play
with a dinosaur,
or a ball,
what can it do?
It eats
and it sleeps.
[BURPS]
And it does that.
[ALL LAUGH]
[GRUNTS]
Aunty Pig,
can I hold the baby?
Yes. If you're very careful,
you can hold Alexander.
Alexander?
AUNTY PIG: That's his name.
Baby Alexander.
NARRATOR: What a big name
for such a small piggy.
It's quite nice,
even though it's a boy.
Goo, goo, goo.
Oh. What's that smell?
Maybe Alexander's
nappy needs changing.
Ew. Disgusting.
Peppa, when you were
a baby, you wore nappies.
I did not.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Mommy, can I play with Peppa
and George in the garden?
[GRUNTS]
Yes.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
Chloé, is it nice having
a little baby brother?
Yes. Alexander
is very sweet.
[GRUNTS]
I wish George was a sweet,
little baby piggy.
I know.
George can pretend
to be a baby piggy.
He can go in my doll's pram.
That's a good idea.
No.
NARRATOR: George does not want
to be a baby.
George, if you pretend
to be a baby,
I promise to be nice
to you forever and ever.
NARRATOR:
George is thinking.
And you can play
with all my toys.
NARRATOR:
George is thinking more.
And when we get home, you
can play with all my toys.
[GRUNTS, GIGGLES]
NARRATOR: George has decided.
What a sweet baby piggy.
[GIGGLES]
[BELLS RINGING]
NARRATOR:
Here are Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep,
Rebecca Rabbit and Zoe Zebra.
ALL:
Hello.
Baa. Why is George
in that doll's pram?
It's not George.
It's a baby piggy.
Goo, goo.
But it is George.
George is a pretend
baby piggy.
ALL: Ah!
Is it a girl or a boy?
It's a girl.
No.
NARRATOR:
George does not want
to be a girl baby.
Okay. It's a boy.
[CHUCKLES]
I've got some cookies.
Would the baby piggy
like one?
Oh, no. It can't eat cookies.
[CRYING]
NARRATOR:
George likes cookies.
Maybe it can have
one cookie.
[LAUGHS]
Goo, goo.
It's so clever.
And so handsome.
[BURPS]
[ALL LAUGH]
It's very funny.
It's the best
baby piggy ever.
NARRATOR:
George likes this game.
Here is Aunty Pig,
with Baby Alexander.
Wow.
A proper, real baby piggy.
It's so gorgeous.
It's much sweeter
than George.
[SOBS]
NARRATOR: Oh, dear.
George liked being
the baby piggy.
Oh, George. You'll always be
my baby piggy.
[WHIMPERS]
Maybe it's time
for a new game.
How about some
dinosaur chasing?
[GIGGLES]
Grrr.
ALL:
Eek! Too scary!
Grrr.
NARRATOR: George liked being
a baby piggy,
but he likes being
George more.
[ALL LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is a lovely sunny day.
Peppa and George are
finishing their breakfast.
[GRUNTS]
Today is a good day
for a cycle ride.
A cycle ride. Yippee!
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
love cycle rides.
Peppa has her bicycle.
[RINGS BELL]
George has his tricycle.
Mommy and Daddy
have their tandem.
What's that?
It's our bicycle.
[HONKS HORN]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
I sit at the front and
Mommy Pig sits at the back.
[GRUNTS]
And we can put these
two seats on the back
for Peppa and George.
But we want to ride
our own bicycles.
George is a bit too little,
his legs will get very tired.
But I'm a big girl,
I won't get tired.
It will be a long cycle ride,
Peppa. Are you sure?
Yes, Daddy, I'm sure.
Okay.
Are we all ready?
Yes, Daddy Pig.
Then let's go.
[BIKE HORN HONKS]
Whee!
I'm winning.
It's not a race, Peppa,
it's just a gentle bicycle ride.
Yes, Daddy,
but I'm still winning.
[RINGS BIKE BELL]
[PANTING]
Ha-ha-ha.
Now we're winning.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY, GIGGLES]
I don't like cycling uphill.
[PANTS]
Peppa, we won the race.
[PANTING]
No, you didn't, Daddy.
Because I wasn't racing
that time.
But now I am.
[GIGGLES]
Can't catch me.
[SNORTS]
Ha, ha.
You cheeky little piggy.
[RINGS BELL]
[LAUGHING]
Hello, ducks.
We're having a cycle ride.
[BIKE HORN HONKS]
[QUACKING]
Hello, ducks!
[HORN HONKS]
[ALL QUACKING]
Ah, I'd forgotten how
much I love cycling.
Oh, I'd forgotten how much
I hate cycling up hills.
NARRATOR: The ground
is getting quite steep.
Ugh. I don't like
cycling up hills.
But look at the beautiful view.
[STRAINING]
My... goodness,
this... is...
hard work.
Mommy Pig.
You're not pedaling.
Oh. Sorry, Daddy Pig,
I was just enjoying the view.
[ALL GIGGLE]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family have
reached the top of the hill.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
All Peppa's friends are here.
ALL: Hello, Peppa.
Hello.
Woof. We're going to have
a race on our bikes.
Baa. Peppa, do you
want to race too?
[GRUNTS]
Okay, as long as we can
race down hill.
Okay.
[KIDS LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends are
going to race down the hill.
[GRUNTS]
Are you all ready?
ALL:
Ready!
You can start,
when I honk the horn.
Like this...
[HONKS HORN]
NARRATOR:
Pedro has set off too soon.
Stop, Pedro!
The race hasn't started yet!
Sorry, Mr. Pig.
I was just letting you know that
the horn sounded like this...
[HONKS HORN]
Whee!
ALL:
Stop! Stop!
Sorry, Pedro, that time
it was my fault.
The next time I honk the horn...
you can go.
Did he say go?
I think so.
ALL:
Go! Go! Go!
Go on, Peppa.
But, Daddy, you didn't
honk the horn.
[HONKS HORN]
NARRATOR:
Danny Dog is in the lead.
Wait for me.
[RINGS BELL]
Whee!
I win.
[GRUNTS]
ALL:
Well done, Peppa!
Yes. I'm very good
at cycling downhill.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
It is home time
for Peppa's friends.
Bye bye, Peppa.
Bye.
Home time for
us too, Peppa.
Mommy. I'm tired.
[GRUNTS]
All this cycling up and down
hills has made my legs tired.
Can I ride
on your bike?
But where will
Daddy Pig sit?
Um... Daddy can ride my bike,
it's very nice.
Oh. Okay.
[HONKS HORN]
[GIGGLES]
I love the tandem.
[GRUNTS]
Daddy, do you like my bike?
Yes, Peppa,
it's very nice.
[ALL LAUGH]
[GIGGLING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are in Granny
and Grandpa Pig's garden.
They're going to play
in their treehouse.
Peppa and George
love their treehouse.
[BELL RINGS]
NARRATOR: Here are Peppa
and George's friends--
Zoe, Suzy,
Rebecca and Richard.
Baa. I like
your treehouse, Peppa.
Can we come in?
Yes.
[SNORTS]
Now we can have a tea party.
[ALL LAUGH]
[BELL RINGS]
NARRATOR:
Here are Pedro and Danny.
Neigh. Hello, Peppa.
Woof. Can we come in?
Sorry, Danny. Only girls can
come into the treehouse.
Boys are a bit noisy.
They always spoil
the tea parties.
But George and
Richard are boys.
[GIGGLING]
Oh. Yes.
Sorry, George.
This treehouse
is for girls only.
[BOTH CRY]
What's wrong?
The girls won't let us
into the treehouse.
Woof. It isn't fair.
Ho. Ho.
I think I can help.
Come over here.
Now we can have a nice,
quiet tea party.
[BANGING]
What's that noise?
[HAMMERING]
[♪♪♪]
There. Now you boys
have your very own den with
its very own drawbridge.
A castle!
Thank you, Grandpa Pig.
[SNORTS]
Can we come in?
No. This is a boys' den.
For boys only.
[GRINDING]
But I love castles.
Castles aren't as good
as treehouses.
[GRUNTS]
Come on, girls.
♪ I'm the king of the castle ♪
[LAUGHS]
Every castle
needs a flag.
BOYS:
Wow.
They've got a flag.
We don't need a silly flag.
NARRATOR:
Here is Granny Pig.
Hello, girls.
Can I get you anything?
GIRLS:
A flag, please.
And it must be better
than the boys' flag.
I'll see what I can do.
♪ I'm the king of the castle ♪
Ho. Ho. Every castle
needs a telephone.
[GRUNTS]
Hold this.
[♪♪♪]
Keep this string
nice and tight,
and you can talk
to the boys.
We don't want to
talk to the boys.
We don't want to talk
to the girls.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
NARRATOR: Granny Pig has found
a flag for the girls' den.
This dress will make
a pretty flag.
[GRUNTS]
Thank you, Granny.
It isn't as good as
the boys' flag.
I wish we were in
the castle.
Fairy princesses
live in castles.
If I were a fairy princess,
I would live in a treehouse.
Can we come over?
Please?
Only if you say
the castle is the best.
It is the best.
[GIRLS GIGGLE]
I'm staying in
my treehouse.
[BRIDGE WHIRRING]
[KIDS GIGGLE]
Baa. I love the castle.
[ALL GIGGLE]
NARRATOR:
Oh dear, it is raining,
and the castle has no roof.
Let's go to
the treehouse.
No. I'll never
leave my castle.
Squeak.
Neigh.
Baa.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
The rain has stopped.
[GRUNTS, GIGGLES]
NARRATOR: George has found
a muddy puddle.
That looks fun.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I'm staying in my castle.
I'm staying in my treehouse.
Ho, ho. I'll look after
your castle, Danny.
I'll look after your
treehouse, Peppa.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Danny love jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles,
whether they are
girls or boys.
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING, GRUNTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING, LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING, GIGGLING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING]